happened
Om Om
[Music]
Do it Do
you also worry about
how will you hold the bells of the disease if you get sick,
how will you bear the expenses If you are also a
good man and are dancing at speed then
definitely watch this video Or first of all let's
know
how many time free health insurance plans are there and which one should
you choose The first one is
accident cover It will take half an inch But if
you ever have an accident due to which you get
injured and you are injured at work then it comes in handy
because it will
give you a big sum And the good thing about it is
that you are a student Insurance companies are
very rare See life insurance
covers are taken in that case if
something happens to our life tomorrow then our family should be
safe But if we have a serious injury
and are on bed and are unable to go to work then
in that case accident cover means that
it gives you money in any way
which will run your household The
second one is playlist cover Critical illness
cover is also there that like if you  If you have
taken a cover of ₹2500000, some diseases are covered in it
like cancer, heart attack,
brain tumor, serious
diseases like these,
God forbid if you get any of these 25-26 diseases, then
an insurance company does
not look into all this at all. How
much are you going to spend on treatment or what are your
expenses because if you have taken a 25 way
critical illness cover, then like a
certificate from a doctor or hospital will be shown
that you have this disease, you will be given
25 opinions at once and later
you will bear your expenses. This
critical illness policy is necessary
because in this you do
not have to show any proof of hospital expenses,
just proof diagnosis is enough.
Thirdly, there is a need to
deal with medicines, hospital, doctor,
so if you take it for ₹5 and have to get
admitted in the hospital for more than a day,
whatever expenses you have for a few months, then that will be
covered, so you should
definitely take this hospital, but there is a lot of concern regarding this.  If you do
n't understand which one to take, then
today we will discuss what is the
first thing for you, the
first thing you have to see is that
how many days' expenses will be covered in Priyanka's suggestion,
Priyanka's supply
system means if you are admitted on 1st
January, then for how many days before and
after that, all your medical expenses will be
covered by this policy, so that at
least 30
days a week, all the expenses before the first edition and the
next new 120 days after the first edition,
cover the children so that
all the expenses of your illnesses for three to four months are
covered, so Priyanka,
you must look at the conspiracy expenses, the second is the
premium, we go to the online website and see
that whatever cover you should take like 10 or 15 lakh,
how much
premium is coming from different insurance companies, sometimes there can be a lot of difference in the premium,
so you
can save money by this, you have seen 34 things, there
is audio room charges, now what happens in this is that you have to see
that in the policy there is single private insurance for
them  Expenses will be borne by you. In many policies,
it happens that we will pay the charges
but only if you resume twin sharing or
general ward.
If it is private then we will
not give it to you in the same form. So, it is
not just a matter of private room. Many times it has been seen
that the better the room, the
better the treatment. When the patients of Mewar get
as good treatment as the one in a
single room, then similarly
you also have to see that the
expenses of staying in a single private room at that place are
also covered in the policy, at least Rs. 10 or 15 thousand. The
fifth thing you have to see is this statement, that is,
if you really ask the insurance company
whether you are admitted in a pass hospital and
you have these expenses, then what is the percentage
chance that the insurance company will pay you the
money.
In 9th science companies, which have the best claim
settlement,
give priority to those companies whose claim settlement
ratio is high. This means that that
company pays the most money in the list.
Many times it happens that
we take a low premium policy but  If the
company does not pay when needed, then in such a situation,
taking a policy with a low premium is
useless. Now you have to see whether
the insurance company has a
tie-up with a good hospital near you, in
which you will
get the facilities. Apart from this, there is a
tie-up between the company and the hospital. If something happens to you in the hospital where you will be admitted,
if your
insurance company does not have a tie-up with that hospital, then the
process becomes quite lengthy.
First you will have to pay money from your pocket,
then
you will have to give the details of the insurance expenses as well. It may take
one, two or three months for you to get your daddy numbers, till then there may be a
problem of gas. So, in this way also you have to
see that you are taking maximum benefit from Bigg Boss
along with the hospital
in your city, so that
you do not have to pay money in the beginning, you bear the entire expense
directly from the insurance company.
Now you are paying attention to the important thing that the
white shirt is only both. The
room settlement should not be through third party
administrative and you should
check the insurance policy yourself and whether the insurance
claim is correct or not.  No, I go
myself to investigate. They say that these are the
claim settlement companies, so I need those companies
which have an in-house settlement department.
Keep one more thing in mind while buying a policy
because nowadays there are many online websites
which sell policies and they are on the phone with you.
While helping you in buying a policy, they try to push the form through you very quickly
because their
interest is that you
get medical relief by any means and they do not have to worry about whether you will get medical relief or not
because they
get money by selling the policy. Keep in mind that
you will not be filling the insurance form in a hurry.
You have to keep in mind that
you will be asked about the diseases you already have, so do
mention your diseases correctly. It may
increase the print a little, but
this gives you a guarantee
that later if the company finds out about your diseases,
it will not be good for you.
See, medicines are expensive, maybe Rs.
10-15000. The premium for a cover of Rs. 5 lakh is
very high, if it is to be paid for everyone then it is very high.
For this, you have a top-up solution,
what happens in this is that if you take a medical and
health insurance policy, for example, of 5
lakh or 10 lakh, then you will need at least 10 or 15
thousand, but you can take a top-up
loan if your expenditure is 5 lakh or
above or above 10 lakh, whichever is decided by the person, then
let's start as to which one you
need, how should it be, first of all
you need more than that, if you feel
that no, then you can get the information that there are top-up loans
in the market
and you can know about that,
if you found this video like spider-man,
then please like my video,
please subscribe and
press the bell icon so that
you get the latest updates and reviews, regarding this, first of all
thank you for watching our
[music]